{"data":[{"question":"She is an ________ girl.","a":"attractive","b":"attracted","c":"attraction","d":"attract","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Someone feels attracted to sth\/someone.\n- Something\/someone is attractive to sbd.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"After your eye test, the ________ will tell you if you need glasses.","a":"dentist","b":"doctor","c":"surgeon","d":"optician","answer":"4","explain":"\n- The optician: someone who tests people's eyes and sells glasses.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"The ________ wanted to write an article about me in the paper.","a":"agent","b":"musician","c":"journalist","d":"announcer","answer":"3","explain":"\n- The journalist: someone who writes news, report for newspaper, magazine.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"I hope the ________ can repair our car quickly.","a":"mechanic","b":"reporter","c":"surgeon","d":"engineer","answer":"1","explain":"\n- The mechanic: someone who skills at repairing vehicles.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"He got drunk after drinking some ________ drink.","a":"rich","b":"strong","c":"clever","d":"powerful","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Strong drink: having taste or small that you notice easily.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"The ________ of the moon for the earth causes the tides.","a":"attractive","b":"attracted","c":"attraction","d":"attract","answer":"3","explain":"\n-The + Noun + of.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"He was ________ right when he said that the man was guilty.","a":"reason","b":"reasonable","c":"reasonably","d":"a reason","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Adverb can modify adjective.\u00a0\nAdv + adj.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"Another word for \"damage\" is ________.","a":"wound","b":"injury","c":"destruction","d":"destroy","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Destruction has the same meaning with damage.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"'To employ' means to ________.\u00a0","a":"borrow","b":"buy","c":"hire","d":"work","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Hire= to be employed by somebody.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"},{"question":"Another word for \"entire\" is ________.","a":"whole","b":"part","c":"strong","d":"completed","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Entire: used when you want to emphasize that you mean all of a group, period of time, amount etc [= whole].","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"30","type":"1"}]}